{
    "subject": "resource/Shooting_at_the_2000_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Women's_skeet",
    "predicate": "ontology/bronzeMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Di\u00e1na_Igaly",
    "human_readable": "Di\u00e1na Igaly won a bronze medal in women's skeet at the 2000 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9730246663093567,
            "question": "What medal did Di\u00e1na Igaly win at the 2000 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9168128967285156,
            "question": "What sport did Di\u00e1na Igaly compete in at the 2000 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8955541253089905,
            "question": "Is Di\u00e1na Igaly known for winning an Olympic medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8835675716400146,
            "question": "In what year did Di\u00e1na Igaly win her Olympic medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8510886430740356,
            "question": "Did Di\u00e1na Igaly win a gold medal at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7963650226593018,
            "question": "Which event did Di\u00e1na Igaly compete in at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7768975496292114,
            "question": "What color was the medal Di\u00e1na Igaly won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7531095147132874,
            "question": "What was Di\u00e1na Igaly's Olympic achievement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6752068400382996,
            "question": "What type of Olympics did Di\u00e1na Igaly participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5238363742828369,
            "question": "Was Di\u00e1na Igaly involved in a shooting sport at the Olympics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Di\u00e1na Igaly won a bronze medal in women's skeet at the 2000 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_304_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of Olympics did Di\u00e1na Igaly participate in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_304_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Di\u00e1na Igaly's Olympic achievement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_304_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What color was the medal Di\u00e1na Igaly won?",
            "html": "dbpedia_304_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_304_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Diana Igaly winning a bronze medal in women's skeet at the Sydney 2000 Olympic Games, which supports the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}